Hi I'm Tiffany, and I'm a self-driving car engineer
こんにちは ティファニーです Mercedes-Benz の
at Mercedes-Benz.
自動運転車のエンジニアです
I work on the localization team and by the end of this module,
ローカライゼーションチームで働いています このモジュールの終わりには
you'll have a good understanding of what I do.
私たちがやっていることが よく理解できると思います
At the moment we are in our Garage at MBRDNA.
今 私たちは MBRDNA のガレージにいます
Hi.
こんにちは
My name is Maximilian, and I also
マクシミリアンです Sunnyvale の
work on self-driving cars at Mercedes-Benz
ローカライゼーションチームの 一部である
as part of the localization team in Sunnyvale.
Mercedes-Benz の 自動運転車に取り組んでいます
In the previous lessons you learned about sensor fusion
前回のレッスンでは センサーの統合と
and how to combine different sensor
共通フィルターを使ったライダーおよび レーダーデータのような
readings like lidar and radar data
異なるセンサーの 読み取り値を組み合わせる方法を
with the help of common filters.
学習しました
You also learned how to write complex code in C++,
C++ での複雑なコードの 記述方法も学習しました
which will be necessary to be successful in the field
これは 自動運転の分野で 成功するには
of autonomous driving.
必要になります
Today you will learn about localization.
今日はローカライゼーションについて 学習します
Localization is what allows an autonomous car
ローカライゼーションを使用すると 自動運転車がいる場所を正確に
to know precisely where it is.
把握することができます
It's an amazing topic, and I love working in this field.
とても素晴らしいトピックで 私は この分野で働くことが大好きです
And of course, localization is really important
もちろん ローカライゼーションは 自立的に運転するには
to drive autonomously.
非常に重要です
Without localization it would be impossible for a self-driving
ローカライゼーションなしでは 自動運転車で安全に運転することは
car to drive safely.
不可能です
At the end also localization lesson you will be able
ローカライゼーションレッスンの終わりには 自動運転車の
to implement high performance localization software and C++
高性能なソフトウェアと C++を
for autonomous cars.
実行できるようになります
So, what is localization?
ローカライゼーションとはいったい何でしょうか?
That's what we are going to cover next.
次は これについて学習します
So let's dive in.
では 始めましょう